Mss.B.St65p
American Philosophical Society
- Series III. Hospitals, Universities and Institutions
  - Institute of International Education, 1958
  - Institute of Nutrition of Central America and Panama, 1951
  - Insurance Institute for Highway Safety, 1970
  - International Academy of Proctology, 1955
  - International Peace Academy, 1971
  - Roscoe B. Jackson Memorial Library, 1946-1952
  - Jeanes Hospital, 1950
  - Jefferson Medical Center: Children and Youth Program, Undated; 2.0 folders
  - Jefferson Medical College, 1955
  - Jewish Hospital School of Nursing, 1945
  - John Hopkins University, 1948-1964
  - Junior League Blood Center, Milwaukee, 1954
  - Kauikeolani Children's Hospital, Hawaii, 1961-1969
  - Knickerbocker Blood Bank, 1956
  - Lancaster Cleft Palate Clinic, 1949
  - Lankenau Hospital, 1971
  - Lederle Laboratories, 1946-1963; 3.0 folders
  - Lilly Research Laboratories, 1951-1963
  - M and R Laboratories, 1951-1952
  - Major Hospital atlas, 1957
  - Mary Imogene Bassett Hospital, 1967
  - Maryland Academy of General Practice, 1963
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health, 1954
  - Massachusetts General Hospital, 1942-1961
  - Maternal Health Center, 1947
  - Mayo Clinic, 1950
  - McNeil Laboratories, 1945-1959
  - Media Clinic, 1965, 1970
  - Medical Clinics of North America, 1962
  - Merck Institute, 1945-1965
  - Merck Sharp and Dohme Research Laboratories, 1959-1961
  - Mercy-Douglas Hospital, 1949-1956
  - Mercy Hospital, 1950-1951
  - Methodist Episcopal Hospital, 1956-1957
  - Michigan Academy of General Practice, 1968
  - Milwaukee Children's Hospital, 1967-1969; 6.0 folders
  - Montefiore Hospital, 1941
  - Montgomery County Association School for Handicapped Children, 1962
  - Montgomery Hospital, 1952
  - Moore Institute of Art, Science and Industry, 1953
  - National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, 1971
  - National Institute of Arthritis and Metabolic Diseases, 1960-1964; 3.0 folders
  - National Institute of Child Health and Human Development, 1961
  - National Institute of Mental Health, 1950
  - National Institute of Neurological Diseases and Blindness, 1962
  - National Institutes of Health, 1946-1964; 3.0 folders
  - New Jersey Department of Health, 1954-1962
  - New Jersey Department of Institutions and Agencies, 1946-1957
  - New Jersey Neuro-Psychiatric Institute, 1954-1958
  - New Jersey Reformatory, Bordentown, 1951-1952
  - New Jersey Reformatory for Women, 1957
  - New Jersey State Colony, 1946-1951
  - New Jersey State Prison, 1946-1953
  - New Jersey Woodbine Colony for Feeble-Minded Males, 1940
  - New York Department of Health, 1956-1957
    City of New York.
  - New York Department of Public Health, 1950-1958
    New York State
  - New York Hospital, 1946, 1951-1952
    Cornell Medical Center
  - New York University Clinic, Undated
  - New York University College of Medicine, 1941
  - Norfolk General Hospital, 1963
  - Northwestern University, 1958
  - Notre Dame University, 1949-1952
  - Oakbourne Colony Hospital, 1952-1962
    Formerly Pennsylvania Epileptic Hospital & Colony Farm, West Chester, PA.
  - Oak Ridge Institute of Nuclear Studies, 1950
  - Office of Civil Defense Mobilization, 1958-1961; 2.0 folders
  - Office of Emergency Planning, 1960-1963; 2.0 folders
  - Office of International Medical Research, 1961-1963
  - Office of Research and Development, 1942-1947; 4.0 folders
  - Ontario Study, University of Western Ontario, 1969-1970
  - Oregon State Board of Health, 1954
  - Pediatric Clinics of North America, 1953, 1960
  - Pennhurst State School, 1945-1955
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1961
  - Pennsylvania Department of Health, 1939-1971; 5.0 folders
  - Pennsylvania Department of Welfare, 1953
  - Pennsylvania Hospital, 1939-1964
  - Pennsylvania School for the Deaf, 1942-1945
  - People's Neighborhood Medical Center, 1971
  - Philadelphia Blood Center, 1941, 1953-1971; 3.0 folders
  - Philadelphia Child Guidance Clinic, 1934-1964; 17.0 folders
  - Philadelphia College of Osteopathy, 1956
  - Philadelphia County Relief Board, 1932-1936; 3.0 folders
  - Philadelphia Department of Public Health, 1939-1971; 6.0 folders
  - Philadelphia General Hospital, 1946-1971
  - Philadelphia Hospital for Contagious Diseases, 1933-1938
  - Philadelphia Psychiatric Hospital, 1955
  - Philadelphia State Hospital at Byberry, 1936-1941; 2.0 folders
  - Playtex Park Research Institute, 1947-1962; 29.0 folders
  - Polk State School and Hospital, 1962-1963
  - Presbyterian Hospital, 1961-1962
  - Project Hope, 1959-1960
    Hospital ship
  - Proposal for a Unified County Child Health Program, 1963
  - Proposals to Children's Bureau, 1961
  - Proposals to create National Institute of Child Health, 1961
  - Psychiatric Facilities for Children, 1951
  - Public Health Research Institute, 1946
  - Queen's Hospital, 1964-1965
  - Rahway Reformatory, 1946-1947
  - Reading Hospital, 1942
  - Rehabilitation Center at Philadelphia, 1958
  - Riddle Memorial Hospital, 1960-1963; 2.0 folders
  - Riverview, 1965-1968
  - Rochester Academy of Medicine, 1962
  - Rochester Regional Hospital Council, 1960-1966; 4.0 folders
  - Ross Laboratories, 1949-1962
  - Rush Hospital, 1937-1946
  - Saint Joseph's College, 1951-1971
  - Saint Joseph's Hospital, 1968
    Elmira, New York
  - Saint Luke's Hospital, 1947-1949
    Bethlehem, Pennsylvania
  - Saint Michael's Hospital, 1955
    Newark, New Jersey
  - Saint Vincent's Hospital, 1950-1958
    Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
  - San Diego Academy of Medicine, 1954
  - Sandhill Medical Cooperative, 1942
  - School District of Philadelphia, 1945-1950
  - Schools for Mentally Challenged Children, 1947-1959, undated
  - Seton Hall College, 1955-1956
  - Seybert Institution, 1948-1958
  - Sheltering Arms, 1940
  - Shreveport Charity Hospital, 1947
  - Sloan-Kettering Institute, 1957
  - Smith, Kline and French Laboratories, 1934-1963; 5.0 folders
  - Spafford Children's Hospital, 1970
  - Specifications for Children's Hospital Units, 1959-1962; 3.0 folders
  - Squibb Institute for Medical Research, 1939-1951
  - Srigley Clinic, 1964
  - Stanford Children's Convalescent Hospital, 1970
  - State University of New York, Buffalo, Undated
  - Swedish Hospitals, 1949
  - Temple University, 1945-1946, 1968
  - Texas Academy of General Practice, 1968
  - Tri-Institutional Facilities program report, 1966
    Philadelphia General Hospital, Children's Hospital of Philadelphia, University of Pennsylvania.
  - United States Army, 1943-1960; 6.0 folders
  - United States Collector of Internal Revenue, 1947
  - United States Committee for the Care of European Children, 1946
  - United States Department of Agriculture, 1935-1939, 1957
  - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1955-1972; 6.0 folders
  - United States Department of Interior-Alaska Native Service, 1948-1954
  - United States Department of Labor, 1941
  - United States Department of State, 1967
  - United States Naval Hospital, 1958-1962
  - United States Public Health Service, 1939-1964; 11.0 folders
  - United States Secretary of Defense, 1953-1954
  - United States War Department, 1941-1947
  - University College of the West Indies: Jamaica, 1949-1956; 3.0 folders
  - University of Arkansas, 1949-1950
  - University of California, San Diego, 1972
  - University of Kansas, 1949-1950
  - University of Maryland, 1957-1962
  - University of Michigan, 1940
  - University of Minnesota, 1946-1960
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1956
  - University of Rochester, 1962-1970
  - University of Texas, 1946-1949
  - University of Virginia, 1945
  - University of Western Ontario, 1969
  - Utah Department of Health, 1955
  - Valley Forge Hepatic and Metabolic Center, 1947-1950; 5.0 folders
  - Van Camp Laboratories, 1950
  - Veterans Administration, 1947-1970; 4.0 folders
  - Victoria Hospital, 1967-1969
  - Villanova University, 1964
  - Vineland Training School, 1949-1967
  - Virus Diagnostic Laboratory, Undated
  - Warner-Chilcott Research Laboratory, 1954
  - Wayne State University, 1945, 1961
  - Well-Baby Clinic, 1935-1936
  - West Virginia American Academy General Practice, 1964
  - West Virginia University, 1963
  - Western Pennsylvania Hospital, 1957
  - Wistar Institute, 1958-1971; 5.0 folders
  - Woman's Hospital of Philadelphia, 1949
  - Woman's Medical College of Pennsylvania, 1946-1963
  - Woodbine College for Feeble-Minded Males, 1950-1955
  - Woods Schools, 1941-1970; 45.0 folders
  - Works Project Administration, 1941
  - Wyeth Laboratories, 1946-1958
  - Yale-New Haven Medical Center, 1960
  - Yonkers Hospital, 1942
  - York Hospital, 1964-1965
- Series IV. Children's Hospital of Philadelphia
  - Administration, 1946-1952, 1961
  - Administrator's Report, 1946-1947
  - Advisory Committee, 1961; 2.0 folders
  - Allergy Clinic, 1951, 1953
  - Annual Report, 1951
  - Appointments, 1964
  - Auxiliary Committee, 1952-1953, 1967
  - Bioassay, 1935-1937
  - Board of Managers, 1927-1956; 5.0 folders
  - Building plans, 1938-1960, undated; 3.0 folders
  - Camp, 1948-1955
  - Cardiac Program, 1939-1941
  - Centennial, 1954-1955; 4.0 folders
  - Chapple-Strauss Syringe, 1954-1958
  - Cleft Palate Clinic, 1947-1950
  - Commission on Accreditation, 1956
  - Committee for Coordination of Neuropsychiatric Programs, 1956-1957
  - Committees, 1937-1972
  - Comptroller's Office, 1935-1945; 2.0 folders
  - Constitution, by-laws, rules, 1941, 1950, undated; 2.0 folders
  - Contributors, 1943, 1950-1953
  - Correlation Clinics, 1947-1957; 6.0 folders
  - Correspondence, 1928-1971, undated; 7.0 folders
  - Curriculum Committee, 1946-1950
  - Dedication Planning Committee, 1954
  - Department for Prevention of Disease, 1916-1942, undated; 2.0 folders
  - Development Fund, 1953-1956, 1970-1971
  - Endocrine Division, 1955
  - Epilepsy Clinic, Undated
  - Evaluation Center, 1957
  - Executive Committee of the Medical Staff, 1924-1972, undated; 11.0 folders
    See also Staff.
  - Executive Committee of the Visiting Staff, 1955-1956, undated; 2.0 folders
    See also Staff and Visiting Staff.
  - Fee Schedule for Drs. Stokes, Bridgers, and Reilly, 1958, 1960
  - Financial Records, 1933-1964; 22.0 folders
  - Fund Raising Drive, 1952, 1962-1969; 6.0 folders
  - Future Plans, 1962
  - Geist Laboratory, 1938-1939
  - Grants in Question, 1933-1935
  - Ground-Breaking Ceremony, 1968
  - History, 1930, 1950, 1965, undated
  - Inactive File, 1936-1939; 2.0 folders
  - Laboratory, 1935, 1947-1956
  - Library, 1946-1955
  - Memoranda and Notices, 1932-1968, undated; 2.0 folders
  - Milk Institute, 1953-1954
  - Miscellaneous, 1939-1967, undated
  - New Building, 1950-1953; 2.0 folders
  - Notes, Undated
  - Nursing Department, 1945-1972
  - Oxygen Therapy Service, 1955
  - Penicillin Procedure, 1947
  - Pennsylvania Company, 1942
  - Pennsylvania Hospital Fund, 1939
  - Planning Committee, 1946-1962
  - Planning Conference, 1961-1965; 2.0 folders
  - Plasmapheresis Study Grant, 1955-1957; 2.0 folders
  - Premature Room, 1947
  - Psychiatric Unit, 1960
  - Public Relations, 1949-1971, undated; 3.0 folders
  - Radiology, 1951
  - Rebound Children and Youth Program, 1966
  - Relocation, 1962
  - Research Budget, Undated
  - Research Department, 1924-1970; 13.0 folders
  - Research Foundation, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1938
  - Research Grants, 1949-1962, undated
  - Research Laboratory Expenditures, 1932-1933
  - Residency, 1941-1953; 2.0 folders
  - Residency Committee, 1954-1956
  - Resident's Manual, 1951-1953; 2.0 folders
  - Rheumatic Fever, Undated
  - Roentgenology, 1950-1951
  - School of Nursing, 1938-1941
  - Serum Exchange, 1934-1964; 6.0 folders
  - Social Service Department, 1947, 1954
  - Staff, 1924-1970; 8.0 folders
  - Statistical Data, 1942-1950
  - Stokes-Personal, 1927-1967
  - Study of Hospital Units, 1958-1961
  - Study of Laboratory Tests, 1960
  - Supplies, 1936-1957
  - Surgical Service, 1946
  - Survey, 1946
  - Tax Material, 1958-1959
  - Third-Year Students, 1957
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1960-1961
  - University of Pennsylvania Pediatrics, 1937-1964, undated
  - Virus Diagnostic Laboratory, 1946-1953; 4.0 folders
  - Visiting Staff, 1930-1956; 13.0 folders
    See also Executive Committee of the Visiting Staff.
  - Volunteer Service, 1950-1951
  - W-133 Study, 1958-1964, undated; 5.0 folders
  - Wolfson Estate, 1960, undated
  - Wortman, Herbert, 1951-1957; 7.0 folders
  - X Ray Department, 1952
- Series V. University of Pennsylvania
  - Administration, 1911-1939
  - Alumni Day, 1959-1960
  - Bicentennial Celebration, 1937-1941; 3.0 folders
  - Commercial Organizations, 1947
  - Committee for Professor of Pediatrics, 1957
  - Committee on the Advancement of Research, 1946-1953
  - Committees, 1935-1972
  - Comptroller's Office, 1947-1951
  - Correspondence, 1936-1971
  - Department of Medicine, 1946-1949
  - Development Fund, 1949-1957
  - Faculty Club, 1968
  - Financial Aid Study Committee, 1970
  - Hospital, 1929-1970, undated; 11.0 folders
  - Hospital-Committee on Post-War Development, 1944-1945
  - Hospital-Department of Orthopaedic Surgery, 1946
  - Hospital-Department of Surgery, 1946
  - Hospital-Financial, 1961-1962
  - Hospital-Future Plans, 1947
  - Hospital-Group Diagnostic Clinic, 1950-1952
  - Hospital-Medical Board, 1936-1957; 11.0 folders
  - Hospital-Pediatrics Residency, 1944-1955; 5.0 folders
  - Hospital-Psychiatry, 1950-1951
  - Hospital-Rules, 1952
  - Hospital-Staff, 1928-1939; 2.0 folders
  - Hospital-Ward G, 1924-1952; 4.0 folders
  - International Services, 1969-1971
  - Eli Lilly Fellowships, 1932-1938
  - Lowenberg Prize, 1938
  - Marriage Council of Philadelphia, 1955
  - Medical Alumni, 1949-1950, 1970
  - Medical Information Office, 1964
  - Medical Library News, 1967-1970
  - Meetings, 1933-1971
  - Memoranda, 1942-1971
  - Miscellaneous, 1945-1967
  - Office Manager, 1947-1951
  - Office of International Services, 1969-1970
  - Parking, 1954-1956
  - Patent Policy, 1966
  - Pediatric Technique Book Fund, 1950-1957
  - Personnel Office, 1939-1944
  - Phipps Institute, 1939, 1955-1972
  - Photographic Service, 1947
  - Policy for the use of human subjects in clinical research, 1962-1966
  - President, 1963-1970
  - Reports, 1930-1972; 3.0 folders
  - Retirement plan, 1948-1950
  - Salt Metabolism Fund, 1933-1940
  - School of Medicine, 1936-1969; 2.0 folders
  - School of Medicine-Chair of Medicine, 1945-1947
  - School of Medicine-Correlation Clinics, 1954-1956
  - School of Medicine-Curriculum, 1933-1954; 3.0 folders
  - School of Medicine-Dean John McK. Mitchell, 1948-1955; 2.0 folders
  - School of Medicine-Dean William Pepper, 1933-1945; 4.0 folders
  - School of Medicine-Dean Isaac Starr, 1945-1948
  - School of Medicine-Department of Community Medicine, 1971-1972
  - School of Medicine-Department of Pediatrics, 1924-1958; 11.0 folders
  - School of Medicine-Department of Psychiatry, 1949-1962; 6.0 folders
  - School of Medicine-Department of Public Health, 1953
  - School of Medicine-Development Fund, 1927, 1947-1949; 2.0 folders
  - School of Medicine-Examinations, 1925-1950; 3.0 folders
  - School of Medicine-Faculty Council, 1946-1969; 9.0 folders
  - School of Medicine-Female Students, 1949
  - School of Medicine-Finances, 1948-1955; 2.0 folders
  - School of Medicine-Alfred Gelhorn, 1970
  - School of Medicine-Internships, 1947, 1951
  - School of Medicine-Lecture Schedules, 1940-1951; 4.0 folders
  - School of Medicine-Library, 1949-1953
  - School of Medicine-Pediatric Faculty, 1924-1939
  - School of Medicine-Preceptors, 1950
  - School of Medicine-Refresher courses, 1946-1948
  - School of Medicine-Survey of Clinical Medicine, 1954-1956
  - School of Medicine-Teaching, 1924-1951; 2.0 folders
  - School of Nursing, 1947, 1951
  - School of Occupational Therapy, 1952
  - School of Social Work, 1950-1959; 5.0 folders
  - Science Center, 1970
  - Senate, 1946-1961; 6.0 folders
  - Space and Equipment, 1954
  - State Labor Laws, 1937-1938
    Pertaining to women
  - Student aid, 1934-1936
  - Therapeutic Standards Committee, 1966
  - Vacation regulations, 1946-1952
  - Vice President of Medical Affairs, 1940-1948
- Series VI. Diseases and Treatment
  See also Series VII.
  - Adrenocorticotropic hormone, 1949-1951; 3.0 folders
    With Armour Laboratories Report.
  - Air-borne Infections-Commission on cross-infections, 1941-1943; 2.0 folders
    Commission on Cross-Infections; Miss Sommer.
  - Air-borne Infections-Miss Sommer, 1940
  - Air-borne Studies, 1937-1945; 11.0 folders
    Includes notes on electrical equipment.
  - Amber Light Period, Undated
    Thoughts toward prevention [of alcoholism]
  - Antibiogram, Undated
  - Application of Clonal selection to Medical practice, 1971
  - Arthritis and Metabolic Diseases Program, 1958-1965, undated; 24.0 folders
    Project Committee.
  - Arthritis and Rheumatoid Arthritis, 1949
  - Ascorbic Acid, 1943-1945
  - Aureomycin, 1950
  - Blood Glucose Tolerance, Undated
  - Blood Plasma, 1956
  - Bright's Disease in Children, Undated
    Roundtable discussion: Lyttle, Aldrich, Landis, Van Slyke.
  - Cancer, 1941-1962
  - Cerebral Palsy, 1948-1960; 4.0 folders
  - Commission on Air-Borne Infections, 1942-1945; 4.0 folders
  - Commission on Liver Disease, 1953-1954
  - Commission on Measles and Mumps, 1943-1945; 5.0 folders
  - Commission on Plasma Fractionation and Related Processes, 1946-1963; 12.0 folders
  - Commission on Viral and Rickettsial Diseases, 1946-1950
  - Commissions on Various Diseases, 1942-1944; 3.0 folders
  - Committee on Blood and Blood Derivatives, 1949-1951; 7.0 folders
  - Committee on Plasma and Plasma Substitutes, 1963-1964; 4.0 folders
  - Committee on Sterilization of Blood, 1955-1956
  - Committee to Investigate the Control of Heroin, 1972
  - Congenital Anomalies, 1961
  - Congo Red Test, 1948
  - Cooley's Anemia, 1949
  - Cubicles, 1938-1939, undated
  - Curare, 1942
  - Cystic Fibrosis, 1955-1964; 19.0 folders
  - Dehydration in Infants, Undated
  - Developmental Medicine and Child Neurology, Undated
  - Diarrhea, Undated
    Preliminary Report--St. Francis Hospital, Trenton, NJ
  - Diets, Undated
  - Drugs, 1960, 1971-1972
  - Epidemiology of Poliomyelitis, 1947
  - Epidemiology of Viral Hepatitus A, 1952-1953
  - Etiology of Viral Hepatitis, 1962-1963
  - Evaporated Milk Studies, 1933-1936, undated; 5.0 folders
  - Feeding and Care of Children in War-Devastated Countries, Undated
  - Gamma Globulin, 1943-1971, undated; 8.0 folders
  - German Measle Research, 1970
  - Globulin: Chicken Pox, 1943
  - Globulin: German Measles, 1943
  - Globulin: Jaundice Prophylaxis, 1944
  - Globulin: Measles, 1944-1946; 2.0 folders
  - Globulin: Received and Dispensed, 1944-1946
  - Globulin: St Vincent's Hopital, 1944; 2.0 folders
  - Globulin: Scarlet Fever, 1944
  - Glycol Vaporizing and Device, 1945-1950
  - Hawaii Cardiovascular Study, Undated
  - Health Examination Survey, 1961
  - Heparin, 1939
  - Hepatitis, 1944-1969; 6.0 folders
    See also Series VII Works by Stokes.
  - Hepatitis Study, 1944-1955; 4.0 folders
  - Hepatitis Symposium, 1969
    Screening tests for carriers
  - History of Preventive Medicine, Undated
  - History of the Commission on Air-Bourne Infections, 1941-1945
    Army Epidemiological Board, U.S. Army
  - Immunization in Viral Hepatitis, 1959
  - Immunopheresis, 1953
  - Influenza, 1933-1961; 23.0 folders
  - Interferon, 1966-1970
  - Inventory of Opium, 1937-1941
  - Japanese B Encephalitis, 1969-1971
  - Leukemia, 1954
  - Lyophile Serum, 1933-1937; 4.0 folders
  - Maternal and Child Health, 1939-1943
  - Measles, 1930-1969; 45.0 folders
    With some information on mumps.
  - Medicine to eliminate nerve and muscle disorders, 1962-1963
  - Mental Retardation, 1964, 1969
  - Milk, 1931-1944; 7.0 folders
  - Moorestown Project: Polio Vaccine Experimentation, 1957
  - Mouse viruses, Undated
  - Mumps, 1942-1959; 23.0 folders
  - Orange drinks, Undated
  - Participation of Prisoners in Clinical Research, 1962; 2.0 folders
    Law-Medicine Research Institute, Boston University
  - Pediatrics, 1939, 1946-1972; 24.0 folders
  - Penicillin, Undated
  - Perspectives in Biology and Medicine, 1970
  - Perspectives in Virology, 1962
  - Philadelphia Chronic Pediatric Disease Program, Undated
  - Physiology and Pathology of the New-Born, 1946
  - Plasmapheresis, 1952-1970; 3.0 folders
  - Poliomyelitis, 1933-1961; 14.0 folders
  - Poliomyelitis-photographs, 1951-1952
  - Preventive Medicine, 1964-1970; 3.0 folders
  - Promin in Tuberculosis, 1941-1943
  - Psychomatic Medicine, 1946
  - Rheumatic Fever, 1944-1952
  - Serum Experiments, 1941-1943; 3.0 folders
  - Spotted Fever, 1939-1940
  - Staph Infection, 1958
  - Streptomycin, Undated
  - Studies on the Toxicity of influenza viruses, Undated
  - Subcommittee on Liver Disease, 1947
  - Subcommittee on Plasma, 1953-1963; 10.0 folders
  - Sulfonamides Study, 1941-1944; 3.0 folders
  - Symposium on viral hepatitis, 1961-1962
  - Syphilis, 1946-1947
  - Tetracyeline, Undated
  - Thymus, 1963
  - Tuberculosis, 1954
  - Ultra-Violet Radiation, 1948-1949
  - Ultraviolet Sterilization, 1956-1957
  - Vaccines, 1963-1964
  - Varicella-Herpes Zoster Group, 1957-1958
  - Viral and Rickettsial Infections, 1958-1959
  - Viral Diseases, 1959
  - Viral Hepatitis, 1947-1964; 4.0 folders
  - Virology, 1971
  - Virus Meningo-Encephalitis, 1961-1962
  - Viruses, 1958-1959
  - Water, 1938-1946; 2.0 folders
- Series VII. Works by Stokes
  - Academic and professional advancement, 1923-1928
  - Academic Pediatrics, 1960
  - Antirachitic value of irradiated evaporated milk, 1935
    ...and irradiated whole fluid milk in infants, an in-patient study. With Molton Rapoport.
  - Arthritis and Metabolic Diseases Program, 1962-1963; 2.0 folders
  - Banana Research, 1935-1938
  - Bibliography, 1927-1971; 2.0 folders
  - Biographical Data, 1953-1972
  - Biological Abstracts, 1939-1969; 2.0 folders
  - Biosciences Information Service of Biological Abstracts, 1970-1971
  - Case of Aplastic Anemia, 1933
    ...showing hematologic response to ingestion of spleen previously incubated with duodenal juice. With F. Curtis Dohan.
  - Cerevim Study, 1943-1945
  - Chapters, Undated
  - Children's Hospital of Philadelphia, History of, Undated; 3.0 vol.
  - Coming of Age of Air-borne Infection, 1959-1960, undated; 2.0 folders
  - Consultancies, Undated
    Genesee, Rochester, East Bay, Buffalo.
  - Correction in A History of Poliomyelitis, 1971-1972
    A contrast in subjective and objective conclusions.
  - Emanuel Friedman Lecture, 1962-1964
    Denver, Colorado
  - Epidemic Influenza, Undated
  - Globulin Research, 1944-1946
  - Graduate Education as related to suburban hospitals, Undated
  - Helium Research, 1935-1937
  - Heparin Research, 1938-1939
  - Hepatitis, 1950-1951, undated; 5.0 folders
    Recent advances in the study of mumps and viral hepatitus; Use pf a skin test in studies of viral hepatitus; Evaluation of the length of protection provided by immune serum globulin during epidemics of infectious hepatitus; Human thrombin as an etiological agent in homologus serum hepatitus.
  - Hepatitis: a bibliography, Undated
  - Herpes Research, 1939-1941
  - Hospital Practice and Stoke's Interview, 1972
  - Influence of adrenal cortical hormone, Undated
    ...on salt retention in four cases of intestinal intoxication in infants. With Mitchell Rubin, Dorothy Asher.
    Incomplete
  - Jaundice Research, 1942-1945; 5.0 folders
  - Lecture notes, Undated
  - Lecture on Water Metabolism, Undated
  - Lectureships, 1955-1956
    Hepatitis I and II
  - Thorvald Madsen Memorial lecture, 1969-1971; 3.0 folders
  - Measles Paper--Notes, 1940
  - Notes for speech at Haverford College, Undated
  - Packard Lecture, Undated
    Mutual aid among organisms with a note on immunization against certain viral infections by natural routes.